shesaidbeauty.com 2019-03-06

# www.unprofessionalbeautyblog.com

We know that your privacy is very important to you and that is why protecting your personal information is the highest priority here at  **She Said Beauty Blog**. To help you better understand the serious measures we take to ensure the privacy of your information, we have prepared this Privacy Policy to inform you about what we collect, use, disclose and manage your personal information. When you provide personal information to us, you are consenting to the manner in which **She Said Beauty Blog** will collect, use, disclose and manage your personal information, as set out below. In this policy, the words “we”, “our”, and “us” refer to **She Said Beauty Blog** and the phrase “personal information” means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), address (city, state, zip), e-mail address, telephone number and etc. We work very hard to safeguard your information, and please be assured that we will never sell your personal information to third parties. ** **

**Personal Information Collection**

We may collect personal information that you provide us when you (i) request certain information about our blog and/or the blog contents; (ii) sign up or register for blog account, e-mail subscription, and/or special offers; (iii) download, use and interact with our mobile applications and services; (iv) contact us via email and/or the Contact Us form on this blog; (v) enter into a contest, giveaway, or sweepstakes or respond to one of our surveys; or (vi) provide us with comments or suggestions. ** **

**Personal Information Disclosure**

We value and respect your privacy so we only use your personal information that you provide us to offer you the best experience on this blog. We want you to know that **She Said Beauty Blog** will not trade, rent or sell your personal information, without your prior consent, except as otherwise set out herein.

  * If you entered into any of our contest, giveaway, or sweepstakes, and prize(s) are being shipped to you, we will share your shipping information on a confidential basis with our delivery service providers such as the U.S. Postal Service, Canada Post, United Parcel Service, Federal Express or other delivery carriers we selected. Our delivery service providers are prohibited from using your personal information for any purpose other than making and to ensure the correct delivery of your prize(s).
  * We must provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of fraud prevention or investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We may also disclose personal information to assist us in protecting against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions.
  * In general, you can visit our blog without telling us who you are or provide us with any information. However, we may collect IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all visitors to our blog and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our blog. We use this information to monitor and improve our blog.
  * Our blog may include links to third party websites. We will not provide any of your personal information to these third parties without your prior consent. We provide links to third party websites as a convenience to the user. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement of any other company, its websites, or its products and/or services. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we recommend that you read carefully. We have no control over such websites and therefore have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose and otherwise treat your personal information. ** **

**Security Measures**

We will maintain the confidentiality of all personal information collected on our blog and will only disclose such information to people, company, and/or third parties who require such information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We work hard on safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. However, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us on our blog.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act imposes requirements on websites that collect personal information about children under 13 years of age. Our policy is not to knowingly collect any personal information on any person under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to our blog for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files.

**California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or affiliates for direct marketing purposes. This notice also includes the name and address of any third parties or affiliates that receive any personal information. For any California resident who wants a copy of this notice, please contact us via email at **justask@shesaidbeauty.com** or through the [**Contact**](https://www.shesaidbeauty.com/contact/) form on this blog.

**Policy Changes**

This Privacy Policy replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to change this policy and to apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. If there are changes to this policy, we will notify you by posting the policy changes on our blog. We want to assure you that we are dedicated in protecting your privacy. If you have any questions regarding how we collect, use and manage your personal information, any concerns about our Privacy Policy or want to let us know your personal information sharing preferences, please contact us via email at **justask@shesaidbeauty.com** or through the [**Contact**](https://www.shesaidbeauty.com/contact/) form on this blog.

Updated: May 25, 2018.
